Kontakt

www.linkedin.com/in/ christinakaiser2 (LinkedIn)

Top-Kenntnisse

Public Relations
Unternehmenskommunikation
Digitales Marketing

Languages

Spanish (Elementary)
Russian (Elementary)
German (Native or Bilingual)
English (Full Professional)

Honors-Awards

Bachelors degree with honor

Christina Kaiser

Manager Strategic Communications bei E.ON SE Essen

Zusammenfassung

Communications professional with profound knowledge in Internal, Financial and Social Media Communications; about eight years' experience within international companies; combination of strategic expertise with an open-minded and creative thinking; passion for digital media and engaging stories

Berufserfahrung

E.ON

Manager Strategic Communications August 2019 - Present (2 Jahre 8 Monate) Essen

GEA Group

Editorial Lead, Internal Communication Dezember 2016 - Juli 2019 (2 Jahre 8 Monate) Düsseldorf und Umgebung, Deutschland

- Responsible for content creation on all internal communication platforms such as internal newsletters, employee magazine and intranet
- Responsible for top management communication
- Providing strategic advice and counsel to managers at all levels
- Building on and managing existing internal communication channels and exploring new

and innovative ways of communicating

- Developing internal tone of voice guidelines and communication consistency through the organization
- · Acting as a communication partner for selected key projects

1&1 Internet SE PR Manager Corporate PR Juni 2013 - Dezember 2016 (3 Jahre 7 Monate) Montabaur

- Spokesperson on topics related to finance, employer branding, logistics and customer service
- Responsible for content creation on the company website, the intranet and all social media channels
- Organizing internal and external events such as press conferences
- Monitoring and evaluation of all communication activities (press clippings, social media
- Responsibility for trainees and interns monitoring, media resonance analysis)

Ausbildung

TH Köln

Social Media Manager · (2016 - 2016)

Universität Paderborn

Bachelor of Arts (Two-subject Bachelor), Media science, German literatures · (2010 - 2013)